巴里  拜托
Barry, please!
那不是我
That's not me!
这不可能
This can't be happening.
你是个真人吗
Are you real?
不  你当然不是
No, of course you're not.
没错了
That's it. That's it.
我终于疯了
I've finally lost it.
没事的  我是个真人
It's okay. I... I'm real.
我的老天...
Oh, my...
我...
I...
我
Oh, I... I...
不敢相信我在和另一个人说话
I can'believe I'm talking to another person.
我已经独自一人好久了
It's been so long.
慢着  我认得你
Wait, I know you--
你和你丈夫  约瑟夫·卡弗
you and your husband, Joseph Carver,
你们成立了麦克洛奇技术公司
you founded McCulloch Technologies.
你是伊娃·麦克洛奇
You're Eva McCulloch.
但你不是应该已经死了吗
But you're supposed to be dead.
不
No.
我没死
Not dead.
只是被困住了
Just trapped.
现在你也一样
Now so are you.
闪 电 侠
第六季
第十二集
在此之前  这个地方是
You see, until now, this place was a whole world
只有一个居民的世界
with one inhabitant...
-就是我  -这里一定是另一个地球
- Me. - This must be another Earth.
是同一个地球  不同的维度
Same Earth. Another dimension.
是中城的一个镜像
You see, a mirror-version of Central City.
同样的城市  同样的建筑  只不过是空的
Same city, same buildings, just empty.
《用作互相的子粒子原亚及论理子量》
你到底是谁
Who are you anyway?
我叫爱瑞丝·韦斯特艾伦
I'm Iris West-Allen.
我是《中城公民报》的记者
I'm a reporter for "The CC Citizen."
从没听说过
Never heard of it.
不过那也无所谓
Not that it matters.
老天  不用一个人自言自语
God, it feels so good to have a conversation
感觉真是太好了
that's not one-sided.
所有东西都是反着的
Everything is backwards.
伊娃  你刚说这个地方
Eva, you said that this place
是我们的世界的镜像
was a mirror-version of our own.
这怎么可能呢
How is that possible?
你这么想
Think of it like this:
我们的现实是从三个维度观察的
our reality is observed by three dimensions:
宽度  深度  还有长度
width, depth, and length.
超弦理论提出这样的假设
The superstring theory posits
还有其他现实的存在
that there are other realities,
人类无法看到的分形维数
fractal dimensions humans can't see.
所以
So...
如这张纸的两面
Two sides.
一面  是我们的世界
One, our world.
另一面不过是虚空的映射
The other is just some empty reflection.
我是一名量子工程师
I'm a quantum engineer.
这  这是我的本行
It's... It's my wheelhouse.
对了  这是这个维度的一个副作用
Yeah, that is a side-effect of this dimension.
我...  我已经习惯了
I... I barely notice them anymore.
你是怎么来到这里的  伊娃
How did you end up here, Eva?
六年前
Six years ago,
我在研发一项技术
I was developing the technology
用以打开通向其他平行世界的大门
to open doors to other planes of existence.
我当时在我的办公室里
I was in my office
就是哈里森·威尔斯的梦想破灭的那晚
the night Harrison Wells' dream went up in smoke.
粒子加速器开始运行
从那以后我就一直在这里
I've been here ever since.
暗物质肯定覆盖了这面镜子
Dark matter must have washed over that mirror
创造了一个入口
and created a doorway.
我被拉进这个世界的时候也在这个办公室里
I was in this office when I got pulled in too.
但事情并非这么简单
But that's not all.
镜子那头还有另一个人
There is someone else on the other side of that mirror,
另一个我
another me.
这怎么可能呢  伊娃
How is that possible, Eva?
那是由镜子所引起的一个分形变量
A fractal variable caused by the mirror.
你的一个复制品
A duplicate of you.
你是说这镜子把一个冒牌克隆版的我
You mean the mirror left a fake clone of me
留在了真实的世界吗
in the real world?
我们得离开这里
We're getting out of here.
我试过了  已经六年了
I've tried. For six years,
我一直身处这个我自己的地狱
I've been in my own personal hell.
伊娃  我必须回家
Eva, I have to go home.
很抱歉你被困在这里了  但是
I'm sorry you're stuck here, but...
我以为我会在这里独自死去
I thought I was gonna die here alone.
至少现在我们有两个人
At least now there's two of us.
调查名流苏·迪尔邦的失踪案
Investigation into the disappearance of socialite Sue Dearbon.
她父母雇我去找寻她已过了274天
Day 274 since her parents first hired me to find her.
调查进度更新
Status update.
毫无进展
Nothing.
雷明顿·迈斯特提供了一条无迹可寻的线索后
Sue's trail went cold in Midway City
苏在米德韦市的线索就断了
after Remington Meister provided a dead end.
名流苏·迪尔邦
令人震惊的晚宴
然而她的确去过那里
However, she was there.
迈斯特证实了这一点
Meister confirmed that much.
你怎么还在这里  不是吧
Hey, what are you still doing here-- oh, seriously?
拉尔夫  昨晚我走的时候
Ralph. When I left last night,
你就站在这里盯着这块板
you were standing here staring at the exact same board,
前晚也是这样
same as the night before.
亲爱的  难道你不觉得是时候找个帮手了吗
Honey, don't you think maybe it's time you got a little help?
然后再洗个澡
And a shower?
塞西尔  我查案就是这样
Cecile, this is my process.
只有跟得上我聪慧的侦探头脑之人
I work things out with the only person
我才能与其合作
that can keep up with my beautiful detective mind.
-那只有我  -你可以和我一起合作
- Me. - You could work with me.
我们一起抓到联邦应急管理署的那个人
We took down the FEMA guy together,
感觉真的很棒
that was so great.
你并不喜欢  好吧
You're not loving that, all right.
塞西尔  你了解我的
Cecile, you know me.
我喜欢以自己的方式去查案
I-I like doing things my own way.
拉尔夫
Ralph...
每个福尔摩斯都需要一个华生
every Holmes needs a Watson.
等一下
Hang on.
怎么了
What is it?
几个月前
So a couple months ago,
我在苏的银行账户  信托和信用卡上
I put up these alerts on Sue's bank accounts,
都设置了警报
trusts, and credit cards.
已侦测到银行新状态
点击OK查看
显然  她刚支付了一小笔定金
Apparently, she just made a small deposit on...
中城第十大道4530号24楼
在中城的一所公寓上
an apartment in Central City.
看到没  和你说过
See? Told you.
我需要的搭档只有我自己
Only partner I need is... This guy.
回头见
See you.
中城第十大道4530号24楼
肯定有什么东西死在这里了
Oh, wow, something definitely just died in here.
《凯特科》
莱克斯·卢瑟获得明日之星奖
卡拉和莱克斯·卢瑟
Kara and Lex Luthor?
天呐  这个危机后世界每天越来越难理解
Man, this post-Crisis world gets harder to understand every day.
对吧
Right?
-天呐  -怎么了
- Man. - What's wrong?
与阿姆内特和金面人的那场四人小切磋
I'm still sore from our little double date
让我现在还全身酸痛
with Amunet and Goldface.
真奇怪
So, so weird.
也许你今天应该待在家里
Maybe you should stay home today.
不不
No, no.
你还在研究更多关于黑洞的事吗
Are you working on more Black Hole stuff?
是啊  我想我就差一点点
Yeah, I think I am getting really close
就能干掉这个混蛋了
to taking this son of a bitch down.
嗯
Yeah.
这是镜像枪吗
That's the mirror gun?
嗯  它包含了尖端的反射微芯片技术
Yeah, it contains bleeding-edge reflective micro-chip technology.
如果我能近距离检测这把枪
If I can examine the gun up close,
也许我就能找到一些
then maybe I can find some kind of small clue
这把枪与黑洞有关的小线索
that connects the gun to Black Hole
因为枪是麦克洛奇制造出来的
since McCulloch created it.
枪还在实验室档案馆里  对吧
It's still in the Starchives, right?
是的
Yeah, yeah, it is.
你能去拿给我吗
Could you... get it for me?
解锁这样的武器似乎不是个好主意
I-I mean, unlocking a weapon like that sounds like a bad idea.
巴里  是我啊
Barry, it's me.
我知道
I-I know,
但自从你和卡弗的事之后
but I mean, after what just happened with you and Carver--
如果那把枪落入坏人之手怎么办
w-what if the gun fell into the wrong hands?
就像冷冻枪落入了史纳特手里一样
Just like the cold gun fell into Snart's.
不会的  相信我
It won't, trust me.
爱瑞丝  我当然相信你
Iris, I-- look, you I trust,
但那个企图暗杀你的人
but, the guy who just tried to to have you assassinated,
我就不那么信了
not so much.
如果说黑洞还有一件
I mean, and if Black Hole had a weapon
与镜像枪一样强大的武器
as powerful as the mirror gun,
你根本无法预测会发生什么
I mean, there's no telling what could happen.
是  你说得对  我去...
Yeah, you're right. I will--um,
我去试试别的角度
I'll try a different angle.
我只是想小心点
I'm just being cautious.
是  我知道  我明白
Yeah, I know, I get it.
去玩吧
Have fun.
好吧
Okay.
还真算不上丽兹酒店
Not exactly the Ritz.
趴下
Get down!
搞什么  女士
What the hell, lady?
我刚救了你的命
Hey, I just saved your life.
不用谢了
You're welcome, by the way.
我的天
Oh, my God.
是你
It's you.
你是苏·迪尔邦
You're Sue Dearbon.
正是本人
In the flesh.
那你是
And you are?
没人跟踪我们  我们安全了
No one followed us. We're clear.
苏  我这九个月来一直在找你
Sue, I-I have been looking for you for nine months
希望你不是按时间收费
I hope you don't bill by the hour.
你去哪里了
Where have you been?
还有为什么你的公寓在我眼前爆炸了
A-and why did your apartment explode in my face?
是啊  发生这种事真麻烦
Yeah, hate it when that happens.
我很认真的  是谁设的炸弹
Look, I'm serious. Now who set that bomb?
他们为什么想杀你
Why are they trying to kill you?
以及这种事持续有多久了
And how long has this been going on for?
我的前任  因为我知道太多了
Uh, my ex. Because I know too much.
大概九个月  你问完了
About nine months. You done?
不  我完全没有完
No, I'm most certainly not done.
为什么你的前任会送你爆炸分手礼
Why is your ex sending you explosive candy grams?
便宜货啊
Ooh, the cheap stuff.
你看  等下再喝
Look. Drinks later.
敞开心怀讲述悲剧故事
Spilling your guts to tell a tragic story?
-当下正好  -好吧
- That'd be now. - Fine.
我爱上了一个杀人犯
I fell in love with a murderer.
高兴吗
Happy?
约翰·洛林
John Loring.
原来拥有非凡魅力的梦幻肌肉先生
Turns out Mr. Dreamy Muscles and charisma-for-miles
还是一位黑市的大军火商
was also a major arms dealer on the black market.
为什么洛林想让你死
So why does Loring want you dead?
因为我发现了他的客户名单
Because I stumbled across his client lists,
武器库存  还有其他的一切
weapons inventory, and everything else
这让他展露了丑恶的一面
that exposes him for the bag of crap that he is.
他第一次想要杀我时
The first time he tried to kill me,
我正在睡觉
I was asleep.
那好吧
All right, well...
-你在给谁打电话  滑头  -你父母
- Who are you calling, Slick? - Your parents.
让他们知道你安全了
To let 'em know you're safe.
干什么  我刚换的套餐
What-come on, I just switched plans.
约翰能追踪你的手机
John can track your phone.
你给我父母打电话  他们就死定了
You call my parents, they're dead.
那好  我们去找警察
All right, then, uh, we'll go to the police.
我认识一个警监可以帮助我们
I know a Precinct Captain who can help us.
我上一次这么做的时候  他们也要杀我
The last time I tried that, they tried to kill me too.
约翰买通了所有
John's got cops on the payroll
他做生意城市的警察
in every city he does business.
那你脱身的计划是什么
Then what's your plan to get out of this?
苏  你不能永远在逃跑
Sue, you can't run forever.
谁说我在逃跑
Who says I'm running?
你和洛林在互相狩猎
You and Loring are hunting each other.
所以你才在中城
That's why you're in Central City.
约翰来城里进行大售卖
John's in town for a massive sale.
如果我能拿到他所作所为的确凿证据
If I can get damning evidence on what he's doing,
他就会进监狱
he goes to jail.
而我就能回家
And I go home.
我闻到了迷案的味道
I smell a mystery.
我闻到了
I smell...
过期牛奶
Expired milk.
听着  一切都会没事的
Look, everything is gonna be fine.
你的父母雇我不惜一切手段
Your parents hired me to do whatever it takes
来把你安全带回家
to bring you home safely.
这也是我要做的
And that's what I'm gonna do.
-怎么做  -简单
- How? - Easy.
我会找出洛林  拿到你要的证据
I'm gonna find Loring, I'm gonna get your evidence,
然后送去给中城警局
then I'm gonna take it to CCPD.
等这些都做完  我就会带你回家
And after I do that, I'm gonna take you home.
约翰是个杀人犯  你这是在冒生命危险
John's a killer. You'd be risking your life.
为了我
For me.
如果你被杀了
If you get killed...
我父母要损失一大笔钱
my parents are out good money.
我跟你一起去
I'm coming with you.
1322  1322
1,322. 1,322.
1,322. 1,322. Okay.
伊娃  肯定还有出去的办法
Eva, there has got to be a way out of here
是我们没想到的
that we haven't thought of yet.
没有了
There isn't.
在这里只有两个选项
There's only two options in this place:
生存或者疯掉
survival or madness.
1,322...
伊娃  我老公肯定会来找我的  拜托了
Eva, my husband will be looking for me, please.
这一切都是这么开始的  你还不明白吗
This is how it all starts! Don't you understand?
你在这一动不动以为一切都能好起来
You sit here and you think everything's gonna work out.
你怎么可能永远困在这
You can't possibly stay here forever,
然后1322
and then 1,322.
这就是我试图逃走的次数
That's how many times I've tried to escape this place.
这也是我失败的次数
That's how many times I've failed.
1322次提醒
1,322 reminders
我永远逃不出这个地方
that I'm never leaving this place.
所以你不要
So please don't...
再让我失败一次了
give me another one.
我今天的头发真的好糟
I'm having a really bad hair day.
对不起  我
I'm sorry. I--
我是自己待太久了
I've been alone for a very long time.
你现在不是一个人了
Well, you're not anymore.
我们只需一个出去的办法  伊娃
We just need one way out of here, Eva.
仅此而已
That's it.
山姆·斯卡德
Sam Scudder.
谁
Who?
他是一个坏人  他几年前曾经
He was one of the bad guys. He trapped--
把一个人捆在了镜子里
someone in a mirror a few years ago.
我朋友们把镜子冻到绝对零度才把人救出来
And my friends got him out by bringing it to absolute zero.
我们
We--
伊娃  我们需要找一点液氮就可以
Eva, we just need to find some liquid nitrogen.
我有个实验室在走廊那边
Well, I-I have a lab down the hall.
那里应该会有
There should be some in there.
液氮可以使镜子里的分子运动
The nitrogen should slow down the mirror's molecules
变慢到焓最低的状态
to the lowest enthalpy state possible.
我的天
Oh, my God.
这个没准能行
This could work.
巴仔  早上好
Hey, Barr. Morning.
-早上好啊  -你现在有空吗
- Hey. - You got a sec?
有啊  怎么了  队长
Yeah, what's up, Captain?
这梗我永远玩不腻
Yeah, that never gets old.
有点腻了  听着
Yeah, it kinda does. Um, listen.
上个月在巴顿街有一起火灾
There was a house fire on Batton Street last month.
里面的居住者死于
The occupant died
烟气窒息
of smoke inhalation.
我合计你可不可以再看看这个案子
I'm wondering if you could take a second look.
乔  这个案子已经被定为意外了
Joe, this case was already declared an accident.
是啊
Yeah.
我需要  一个没接触过这个案子的人看一下
I need, uh, fresh pair of eyes on it.
好吧  那你想让我去找什么
Okay, I mean, what am I looking for?
什么都行
Whatever you find.
乔  我已经有一堆案子了
Joe, I mean, I've got a mountain of cases
都还没看呢
I need to go through.
那些还没破掉的案子
Ones that haven't been solved already.
好吧  我只能说
Okay, all I can say
你是在帮我一个忙
is that you'd be doing me a favor.
无论你发现了什么  巴仔
And whatever you find, Barr,
直接汇报给我
bring it directly to me.
行
Okay.
多谢了
Thank you.
这个仓库是属于约翰的
John owns that warehouse.
交易会在这进行
That's where the deal will go down.
你这是要去哪
Where are you going?
-我跟你一起去  -不不不  不行
- I'm going with you. - No, no, no, no, no.
我知道
Oh, look, I get it.
骑士风度是你的作风
Chivalry's your brand.
你是一个麻省理工的学生  会说六种语言
You're an MIT grad, speak six languages,
而且你还会玩马球
and you play polo.
你属于乡村俱乐部  而不是去现场
You belong in a country club, not in the field.
你跟你的维多利亚时代英雄救美那一套
You belong in the 19th Century with your Victorian,
都是属于19世纪的
save-the-damsel-in-distress crap.
洛林不知道我会出现
Loring doesn't know that I'm coming,
所以我有意料之外的成分
so I have the element of surprise.
而你呢
You, on the other hand,
他可能知道你会来
he might kinda know that you're coming.
也就是  请待在车里
Translation: stay in the car, please.
希望洛林穿囚服会好看
I hope Loring looks good in orange.
我想你不是观鸟人吧
Uh, I don't suppose you're a fellow bird watcher?
范·迪塞尔
Hey, Vin Diesel!
你还想我在车里等着吗
You still want me to wait in the car?
所以能不能告诉我你怎么会武术
So you mind telling me how you know martial arts?
我父母把我送到京都待了一夏天
My parents sent me to Kyoto for a summer.
一位盲人老师训练我
Trained with a blind sensei.
-教会了我一切  -真的吗
- Taught me everything I know. - Really?
假的
No.
基督教青年会一个叫弗兰克的教我的
I trained with a guy named Frank at a YMCA.
你能放松点吗
Will you relax?
我们在这很安全  约翰又不傻
We're safe here. John's not stupid.
在公共场所杀我
Killing me in a public place?
不可能的
Uh-uh, it's not gonna happen.
不好意思  我记得他炸了一间公寓
I'm sorry, I believe he blew up an apartment
只为抓你
to get to you.
那个建筑
That building was scheduled
计划下个月拆除
for demolition next month.
但他现在的确知道有人在追他
But he does know that someone's after him now.
会让他更难被抓到了
It'll make him harder to get to.
你的功劳
Thanks to you.
你去哪
Where are you going?
对不起  滑头
Sorry, Slick.
我不能和一个不相信我能
I can't partner up with someone
全力以赴的人搭档
who doesn't think I can pull my own weight.
等一下  苏  等下
Hang on a second, Sue. Hang on.
你能等下吗  拜托
Will you just hang on one second, please?
当我接一个案子
Look, when I take a case,
我一定会坚持到最后
I see it through to the end.
直到你安全才是最后
And this doesn't end until you're safe.
你相信我吗  拉尔夫
Do you trust me, Ralph?
我刚认识你
I just met you.
但你的确救了我
But you did save my keister.
两次  那就是说我欠你
Twice. And that means I owe you.
我是知恩图报的人
And I always pay my debts.
我就当是相信吧
I'll take that as a yes.
所以
So...
-没有那些照片  -我们就退回到起点
- without those pictures-- - We are back to square one.
幸运的是  我们还有约翰的账簿
Fortunately, we still have John's ledger.
他把他所有的交易
He keeps a detailed record of every deal
都详细记录在内
he's ever made in it.
多年的不利于他的证据
Years of evidence against him.
但他的办公室还在
But his office is still on the seventh floor
那个仓库的七楼
of that warehouse.
现在安保措施可能已经加倍了
Which has probably doubled its security by now.
但污水管道系统  那是个好入口
But the sewer system, that's a good way in.
那些地下道直接到达
Those tunnels, they lead directly to the center
-那座建筑中心  -然后我们计时
- of the building. - And then we time our entry
-等护卫  -换岗
- for when the guards... - change shifts.
当我们上楼梯进了洛林的办公室
And then we mosey up the stairs into Loring's office,
我们就得手了
we get the prize.
你确实很滑头嘛
Well, you are slick.
天呐  拉尔夫  你找到她了
Oh, my God, Ralph, you found her!
准确地说  我找到了他
Oh, technically, I found him.
苏·迪尔邦
Sue Dearbon.
塞西尔·霍尔顿  超能力者律师
Cecile Horton. Meta-human attorney.
但我也有二十年
But I also have 20 years of experience
为非超能力者辩护的经验
defending non-meta-humans.
法律是我的游戏  塞西尔是我的名字
The law is my game, Cecile is my name.
不管你遇到什么事  我都能
I can cover you no matter what you've had going on
-帮你  -借一步
all this time. - Just need a quick word.
明白  等下
Oh, gotcha. Just one sec.
是这样  我们  我们
Listen, we're--we're--
我们有点事
we're kind of in the middle of something.
苏过去一年一直在逃亡
Uh, Sue's been on the run for the last year.
事实证明有人在抓她
It turns out that someone's after her.
你是守卫她的铠甲骑士吗
And you're her knight in shining armor?
拉尔夫  我超爱
Ralph, I love it!
顺便说下  你俩
By the way, you two? Hmm.
当我用超能力读取你俩时
When I read the both of you with my powers,
我都分不清你俩谁是谁
I could barely tell you apart.
感性地来说
Like, emotionally speaking,
你和苏频率相符哦
you and Sue are definitely surfing the same wave.
我只想保护她
Just trying to keep her safe.
也不是在约会
I mean, it's not like we're dating.
不敢相信我之前竟然没想到过
I can't believe I didn't think of this before.
你最终会想到的
You would have, eventually.
怎么回事
What's happening?
不
No.
应该能行的
It should've worked.
不
No.
我真的以为能够回到以前的生活了
I really thought I was going back to my old life.
伊娃  你会回去的
Eva, you will.
这都不重要了
It doesn't even matter anymore.
我亲爱的约瑟夫
My sweet Joseph.
我们曾如此相爱
We were so in love.
我在镜子里看着他
I saw him in the mirror.
我这样看了他五年
I watched him for five years
看着他哀悼  悲伤  然后...
as he mourned, grieved, and...
继续生活
moved on.
而我无法
And I can't-- I--
我无法放下
I can't move on.
我的天啊  纳什
Oh, my gosh. Nash.
我没想到这里还会有别人
I didn't think anyone else would be down here.
我把东西丢在这里了
I- I lost something down here, so.
好吧  可以理解
Oh, right. Well, that makes sense.
这实验室档案馆可真大
These Starchives are so massive.
-是的  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
抱歉  你在这里干什么
I'm sorry, what were you doing down here?
西斯科让我在这里镇守
Cisco asked me to hold down the fort
他就...
while he, uh--
他想让我清点库存
He wanted me to take the inventory,
我得照办  太烦了
so I gotta do that. It sucks.
你在说谎
That's a lie.
你在这里干什么
Uh, what are you doing here?
我把诺拉的日记弄丢了
I lost Nora's journal.
好几个星期没看到它了
I haven't seen it for a couple weeks.
而且
And, um...
这是我女儿留下的
you know, it's the only thing I have left
唯一一件东西
of my daughter, so.
-你一定很难过  -你感同身受  对吗
- Ah, must be hard. - You would know, wouldn't you?
现在仔细想想  这可能是...
Now that I think about it, that's probably--
我在揭旧伤疤  或许...
I am digging up the past, and, you know,
或许我应该学着活在当下
maybe I should start living in the present.
我们都应该这样
So should we all.
但是这对你来说很难
But it's difficult for you.
是吗  纳什
Isn't it, Nash?
有太多没完成的事情了
There's so much unfinished business.
听着  纳什
Look, Nash.
好
Right.
巴里不知道这件事
Barry doesn't know about this.
他要是知道我弄丢了诺拉的东西会很难过
He'll be crushed if he knew that I lost anything of Nora's, so.
你可不可以不要告诉他
Could you maybe not mention
我来过这里
me being down here?
也许你应该坦白你为什么在这里
Maybe you should mention why you're down here.
这是我们之间的秘密
It'll be our little secret.
我一向很喜欢你
I always knew I liked you.
哈里森·哈里·威尔斯日记
洛林的办公室就在楼上
Loring's office is right up those stairs.
后到的人买酒
Last one there buys the Gingold.
不许动  站住  否则要开枪了
Freeze! Stop or we'll shoot!
-至少他没有囤积癖  -专心点
- At least he's not a pack rat. - Focus.
-没找到  -加快速度
- Not finding it. - Search faster.
我这里有发现
Think I've got something.
这不是账簿
That's not a ledger.
不  这是一把中城商业银行
No, it's a key for a safety deposit box
保险箱的钥匙
at the CC Mercantile Bank.
我猜你的前男友把账簿藏在了那里
Where I'm guessing your ex hid the ledger for safe keeping.
很好  我们该走了
Good point. Time to go.
我们有麻烦了
Uh, we have a problem.
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
定义相信
Define trust.
抓住我
Hang on.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
有时会
Sometimes?
别松手
Don't let go.
我们刚刚
We just--
你刚刚
You just--
你是伸缩人吗
You're the Elongated Man?
没错  我就是充满了惊喜
Yeah, I'm just full of surprises.
你是怎样变成伸缩人的
How-- how did you become the Elongated Man, anyway?
我被一个秘密组织
I was brutally experimented on
残酷试验了很多年
by a covert organization for years.
他们强迫我服用橡胶类的高分子化合物
They forced me to consume rubber-based polymer compounds.
是真的吗
Seriously?
不是
No.
我乘了趟公交车
I rode a bus.
所以你是个如假包换的超级英雄
So you're, like, an honest-to-God superhero.
那是什么感觉
What's that like?
就跟其他任何你喜欢的工作一样
It's like any other job you love.
非常有满足感
It's rewarding as hell.
但这工时  要说的可就多了
But boy, the hours? Let me tell you.
说真的
Seriously.
你是个...
You're like a...
好人
good person.
我只帮你拿到了钥匙
I helped you get a key.
不是账本
It's no ledger.
洛林的账本肯定在
Well, Loring's ledger
跟这把钥匙配套的
will definitely be in the box
保险箱里
that goes with this.
现在我们知道了保险箱在哪里
Now we know where the box is located.
我们只要打开它就行了
All we have to do is open it.
然后你就可以回到你的生活中
And then you can get back to your life.
听着
Listen...
我想告诉你我有多感激你
I want you to know how much I appreciate you
你愿意把你的秘密托付给我
trusting me with your secret.
这意义重大
It means a lot.
我可以打电话给我中城警局的朋友
I can call my friends at CCPD
拿到洛林保险箱的搜查令
and get a warrant for Loring's deposit box.
应该不会超过一天时间
Shouldn't take more than a day.
我们没有一天时间了
We don't have a day.
洛林已经慌了
Loring's already spooked.
他随时有可能把保险箱拿走
He could move that box at any minute.
我觉得我们唯一的机会就是
I feel like our only chance at--
不  这太疯狂了
nah, it's too crazy.
来吧  跟全班同学分享一下你的想法
Come on. Share your thoughts with the class.
如果
What if...
我们现在就闯进中城商业银行呢
We break into CC Mercantile Bank now?
就我们俩
Just us.
然后我们把账本拿走
And take the ledger for ourselves.
我很肯定这种行为叫做偷窃
Believe that's called stealing.
拜托  滑头
Oh, come on, Slick.
你也是私家侦探
You're also a P.I.
你不会告诉我你一直都循规蹈矩的吧
You can't tell me you've always operated by the book.
不  但我不能犯罪
No, but I can't commit a crime.
我明白了
I get it.
而且我尊重你的意见
And I respect that.
但拉尔夫  我不是英雄
But Ralph, I'm not a hero.
所以如果这是我唯一
So if this is the only chance I have
能再次见到我父母的机会
to see my parents again,
我必须冒险
I have to take it.
苏
Sue...
做个英雄
being a hero,
就是要帮助无辜的人
it's about helping innocent people.
我不会让你一个人去
I'm not gonna let you do this alone.
你不会吗
You're not?
不会
No.
但我们得按照我的方式来
But we do this my way.
我们进去  拿到账本
We get inside, get the ledger,
然后马上把它交给我在中城警局的朋友
and immediately bring it to my friends at CCPD.
做还是不做
Deal or no deal?
做
Deal.
所以  你发现了什么
So? What did you find out?
这些烧焦的痕迹
These scorch marks.
他们像是太阳光通过放大镜
They're giant burns like
产生的那种剧烈燃烧造成的
sunlight through a magnifying glass.
所以你作为犯罪现场调查专家的意见是
So in your expert CSI opinion--
火灾是由紫外线引起的
The fire was started by UV light rays.
就跟光博士烧毁《公民报》的方式一样
Same way Dr. Light torched "The Citizen."
好吧  乔
All right, Joe.
这是怎么一回事
What's going on?
听着  这不是唯一一份
Look, this isn't the only file I found
看起来像是被疏漏掉的文件
where it looks like something had fallen through the cracks.
所有这些案件都牵涉到意外死亡
All of these cases involve accidental deaths.
所有受害人都跟这个叫
All the victims are associated
约瑟夫·卡弗的家伙有关系
with this guy Joseph Carver.
我开始觉得中城警局有人在帮他
I'm start to think that somebody here in CCPD
掩盖这些案件
is helping him cover this up.
你觉得这里有内鬼吗
You think there's a mole here?
卡弗在这里的关系相当深
Carver's influence runs deep, man.
州长  市长  总裁们
Governors, mayor, CEOs.
好吧  好...
Okay, all right, um,
这些是爱瑞丝正在调查的
look, this is what Iris is already investigating.
她的线索和我们去年
Her lead had to do with the Mirror Gun
从麦克洛奇技术公司偷来的镜像枪有关
that we stole from McCulloch Technologies last year.
这线索因为我不肯给她枪而罢休了
It fell through because I wouldn't give it to her.
你为什么没给她
Why didn't you give it to her?
那很危险吗
I mean, was it dangerous?
那可能给她带来危险
I mean, it could put her in danger.
我不信任如果那把枪暴露于世
Yeah, I don't trust what the world might do
这个世界会作何反应
if that gun got out there.
这个世界很疯狂
Yeah, well, the world is crazy,
但毋庸置疑的是卡夫很危险
but it's clear that Carver is really dangerous.
爱瑞丝是你的伙伴也是你的家人
Iris is your partner and family,
我不认为我们现在除了家人
and I don't think we can trust this right now
还可以信任谁
with anybody other than family.
我很抱歉你无法在看到你丈夫了
I'm sorry you're not gonna see your husband again,
但是如果你能接受就会好受很多
but it's easier if you just accept it.
伊娃  你说过你想回到原来的生活
Eva, you said that you wanna go back to your old life.
也许那已经消失  但是你可以从新开始
Look, maybe it's gone, but you can start a new one.
它破裂了我很欣慰
I'm glad it's broken.
反正我也看厌了那个不想要我的世界
I'm tired of looking at a world that doesn't want me anyway.
我受够了等待一个人来救我
I'm tired of waiting for someone to come and rescue me.
我更是听恶心了
And I'm sick and tired of people
别人告诉我一切都会变好的
telling me that everything is gonna be all right.
因为它并不会
Because it isn't.
它永远也不会变好
It's never gonna be all right!
永远不会
Never!
刚刚发生了什么
What just happened?
我想我们找到了出去的方法
I think we just found our way out of here.
你确定这有必要吗
And you're sure this is necessary?
一个可信的消息传到中城警局
A credible tip came in to CCPD
说这个分行是抢劫的目标  所以是的
saying this branch was a target for robbery, so yes.
这是进出保险库的唯一途径
Well, this is the only way in or out of the vault.
内门装有
The inner gate is fitted
防盗电气系统
with an anti-theft electrical system.
在没有管理员钥匙的情况下打开或关闭它
Opening or closing it without the manager's key
会自动激活50000伏故障保险装置
automatically activates a 50,000 volt fail-safe.
把牛关在电栅栏里
An electric fence to keep the cattle in.
聪明
Smart.
谢谢  兄弟
Thanks, pal.
我的老天爷
Sweet Fancy Moses.
我明白为什么我这么做时别人会恶心了
I understand why people are grossed out when I do that.
到你了  滑头
Your turn, Slick.
对了
Oh, right.
除了热衷于搏斗
You know, besides a passion for fisticuffs
你在侦探工作这方面也很有天赋
you've got a real knack for detective work.
你有想过当个侦探吗
You ever think about getting behind a desk?
听起来比我的寄宿学校还糟糕
Ugh, that sounds worse than my boarding school.
或者是那一次我父母
Or the times my parents made me take
让我上骑马课
horseback riding lessons.
亦或是每周六在美国驻巴黎大使馆
Or learning French every Saturday
学习法语
at the US Embassy in Paris.
天啊  你的童年听起来可真糟糕啊
Gee, your childhood sounds just awful.
我没说它很糟糕
I didn't say it was awful.
那只是不是我
It just wasn't me.
真相是
The truth is,
我一直讨厌整个社交名流场合
I always hated the whole socialite scene.
这也是为什么  有一天  我醒来顿悟
Which is why, one day, I woke up and realized
我根本不知道自己是谁
I had no idea who I was.
我想我还是没想明白我到底属于哪里
Guess I still haven't figured out exactly where I belong.
可怜的富家小千金
Poor little rich girl.
她怎么能这么迷茫呢
How could she be so lost?
不  我  我懂的
No, I-- I get it.
我曾经穿着你正穿着的制服
I used to wear that uniform you've got on.
我是个警察  一个很棒的警察
I was a cop. A damn good one.
然后突然结束  我也迷失了
And then that ended abruptly, and I got lost too.
我坐上了那辆公交车  找到了我的归属
And I rode that bus, and found where I belong.
所以你在说我还有希望吗
So you're saying there's hope for me?
在我看来你有
There is from where I'm standing.
所以  伙伴
So, partner.
这是个重大的时刻  你介意我来吗
It's a big moment. You mind if I do the honors?
当然
Of course.
你应得的
You earned it.
找到了
Found it.
一定是个小账本
Must be a tiny ledger.
现在我们去玩《马里奥赛车》怎...
Now what do you say we get out of here and play "Mario Kart"--
搞什么
What the hell?
看来你并不是唯一一个充满惊喜的人
I guess you're not the only one that's full of surprises.
我们就差一点就能拿下洛林
We are this close to taking down Loring.
苏  你为什么要这么做
Sue, why are you doing this?
谁管什么洛林  我根那家伙不熟
Who cares about Loring? I don't even know the guy.
不过我确实
I do, however,
知道他把他的贵重物品都放在哪了
know where he keeps his valuables.
一开始就没有什么账本
There never was a ledger.
说下去
Keep going.
所以你才在中城租了一间公寓
That's why you rented an apartment in Central City.
你知道我一直在寻找你
You knew I was keeping tabs on you,
所以  所以你把我引来
so-- so you lured me in.
你故意设计让你自己的公寓爆炸就为了...
You rigged your own apartment to explode for--
为了什么  就为了让大家相信
for what? Just to sell the story of--
那位惹人喜爱的名媛正在逃亡
of sympathetic socialite running for her life?
你相信了
You bought it.
但别觉得不好意思
But don't feel bad.
你是一个好人
You're a good guy.
也是一个英雄
And a hero.
你估计总是看到别人好的一面
You probably see the best in everyone.
而我  我只看到我想要的东西
Me, I see what I want
然后我就会拿走
and I take it.
你利用了我的侦探思维
You used my detective mind
来找到洛林的储藏箱
to track down Loring's deposit box.
你  你把所有人都耍了
You--you played everyone.
你的父母找你都找疯了
Your parents are desperate to find you.
他们知道你到底是什么样的人吗
Do they even know what you really are?
不  这是我们的小秘密
No. That's our little secret.
如果他们发现自己的独生女是个小偷
If they found out their only daughter was a thief,
他们会崩溃的
they'd be devastated.
所以你对我的身份一定要保密
So you keep your mouth shut about who I am,
而我也会绝口不提你的身份
I keep mine shut about who you are.
可以吗  伸缩人
Deal, Elongated Man?
苏  你告诉我的话里有真话吗
Sue, was anything you told me real?
有
Yes.
也没有
And no.
再会了  滑头
See you around, Slick.
中城警局
CCPD.
你们都被捕了
You're all under arrest.
想得美  警官
Nice try, officer.
但我的储藏箱里有无声警报
But I have a silent alarm on my deposit box.
所以我知道你是偷了我的东西
So I know you stole that from me.
没有手机
No phone.
想伸长穿过这些栏杆
Can't stretch through these bars
一定会被烤熟
without getting seriously toasty.
总是有备而来
Always come prepared.
你不会想这么做的
You don't wanna do this.
不  我想
Yeah, I do.
我就是这种人
I'm that guy.
你别想那么轻易地摆脱我
You're not getting rid of me that easily.
稍等我们一下
Give us a minute.
把他们都杀了
Kill 'em both.
我在你体内吗
I'm inside you?
你知道这有多恶心吗
Do you have any idea how disgusting this is?
我在救你的命
I'm saving your life.
不  你没有  我们不是搭档
No, you're not. We are not partners.
我之前被枪击也没事
I have handled being shot at before.
这真是一点也不稀奇
Why does that not surprise me?
让我出去
Let me out.
可以  我让你出去
Sure, I'll let you out.
不过我之后会送你去铁山监狱
And then I'll take you to Iron Heights
只等这群蠢货子弹用光就好
as soon as these idiots run out of ammo.
你就不能闭嘴吗  做点什么呀
Ugh, do you ever shut up? Do something.
我正在做
I am doing something.
你对现在这种情景有任何帮助吗
What's your contribution to this quaint little scenario?
我想想  没有
Oh, wait, nothing.
这都是你的错
This is all your fault.
总是有备而来
Always come prepared.
你好  苏
我想你身上有属于我的东西
难道就没有不想杀你的人吗
Is there anyone that doesn't want to kill you?
还真没有
Not really.
别跑了  老朋友
我真得要学习西班牙语了
I have really gotta learn Spanish.
你想要钻石吗
You want the diamond?
过来拿啊
Come and get it.
你真是个蠢货
我这个蠢货也能宰了你
好吧
来跳一曲探戈吧
看来我们都被骗了
Looks like we both been had.
她把他削弱了
She softened him up.
我们杀了他
Let's finish the job.
交给你了  韦斯特队长
It's all yours, Captain West.
谢谢你  闪电侠  把他们带走
Thanks, Flash. Clear this out, guys.
兄弟
Hey, bud.
闪电侠
Flash.
是他
It's him.
就是他抢劫了我们
He's the one who robbed us.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你认错人了  先生
That's a case of mistaken identity, sir.
韦斯特队长会解释的
I'm sure Captain West can explain.
没事的
It's all right.
抱歉我没能及时收到消息
Hey man, I'm sorry I got word late,
但是我搜索了这里  紫外线跑了
but I searched the whole area. Ultraviolet's gone.
-我没能阻止她  -别担心  我们会抓住她的
- Couldn't stop her. - But don't worry, we'll get her.
我保证
I promise.
我说的不是紫外线
I wasn't talking about Ultraviolet.
苏·迪尔伯恩  搜索中
洛林已经被逮捕了
Loring's in custody,
但是面部识别系统在中城
but facial recognition isn't picking her up anywhere
找不到她
in Central City.
看来苏·迪尔伯恩消失了
Looks like Sue Dearbon has vanished.
再一次
Again.
这是我的错
That's on me.
她耍得我
She played me, Iris.
就像  克特兰耍萨克斯一样
Like...Coltrane's soprano sax.
约翰·克特兰  爵士乐历史上最伟大的萨克斯管演奏家之一
拉尔夫  你不要为此自责
Ralph, you can't beat yourself up.
你又不知道她是这样的人
I mean, it's not like you knew who you were dealing with.
我应该是侦探大师
I'm supposed to be a master detective!
拉尔夫  我们都曾经相信过
Ralph, we've all put our trust in people
背叛自己的人  谁知道我经历了多少次
who have betrayed us. God knows I have.
我要去拆掉我的犯罪记录板
I'm gonna go tear down my crime board.
他这次可是需要点时间来平复一切了
It's gonna take him a while to get over this one.
乔告诉我你今天去警局了
Hey, Joe told me that you came by CCPD today.
我知道你没和我打招呼的原因
I think I know why you didn't come say hi.
万一它落入坏人之手该怎么办
What happened to it falling into the wrong hands?
在我手里很安全
These are the right hands.
乔和我发现了一些证据  指出卡弗的杀手
Joe and I found evidence linking Carver's assassins
和一些凶杀案的联系
to more killings.
警局以为这些案件是意外事故
Crimes that CCPD thought were accidents.
黑洞比我预想的要危险许多
Black Hole is a lot more dangerous than I even realized.
但是如果你能在调查中用到它
But if you can use this in your investigation in any way
更快地扳倒卡弗和他的手下
to bring down Carver and his people faster,
这就是好事
then that's a good thing.
虽然我不信任世人...
And while I don't trust the world...
但我相信你
I do trust you.
全心全意
With everything.
谢谢
Thank you.
你和镜子有着连接  就算
You have a connection to the mirror, even
它已破裂
when it's broken.
你现在听起来才是疯了
Now who sounds crazy?
过去的六年里  我见过很多奇怪的事
I've seen a lot of strange things in the last six years.
你可以控制镜子是最不怪异的
You being able to control that mirror is the least of it.
萨姆·斯卡德甚至可以在镜子中穿越
Sam Scudder could even travel through them.
我可不是穿过镜子只为了抢银行的
Well, I'm not a meta-criminal who jumps through mirrors
超能力罪犯
to rob banks.
我知道
I know.
你比他们要好
You're much more than that.
这个世界里只有我们两个
We're the only people in this world, Eva,
相信我  你比你自己认为的要坚强许多
so trust me when I say that you're stronger than you think.
你是生还者
You're a survivor.
现在去证明吧
Now prove it.
成功了  现在继续
You did it. Now keep going.
1,323...
我还在你身边
I'm still with you.
我是怎么做到的
How did I do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我保证  我们会弄明白的
But I promise you, we will figure it out.
激光共焦扫描
麦克洛奇遭神秘组织威胁
游戏开始
Game on.